silabsoft.org 2010-06-12

# Silabsoft.org

Silabsoft is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you may provide online here on our site.

### Basic Confidentiality Policy

Silabsoft' policy is that personal information, such as your name, postal, e-mail address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information (such as to reply to your request or to handle your complaint). For example, when you file a complaint about a forum abuse, the personal information you provide will be used to process your complaint **only**.

### No Release of Information to Third Parties

Personal information **will not be released** to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provide the information, such as sending your complaint to the company for action, or if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide your information to third parties and we will never sell personal information to anyone.

### Computer Tracking of Identifiable Information

Our website is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors. It does recognize the IP home server of visitors, but not e-mail addresses. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our site. This information is used only for internal purposes by Silabsoft technical support staff (for example, so that you can not vote in polls from the same IP more than once).

In addition, our web site uses third party services to collect information about the visits to our web sites. For example, they compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our sites, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web sites, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and will not be used to gather such information. We will not use any service which does not have a privacy policy. If you have information that a service uses or gathers personal information, please inform us by contacting us and we will immediately re-evaluate our relations with that third party.

### Third Party Advertising

We use TribalFusion and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp?) In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

### Forum and Chat

Silabsoft has public forums for our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

This site contains links to other sites. Silabsoft staff is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Web sites to which we link or which participate in our programs but are not hosted by us.

Last revised: May 19th , 2008.

Current Visitor Count: 2
